多纳泰罗：网络空间的无数里程已被彻底梳理
Donatello: COUNTLESS MILES OF CYBERSPACE COMBED OVER.
数不清的编程代码行被仔细审查
INNUMEROUS LINES OF PROGRAMMING CODE SCOURED.
海量的字节、节点与缓存经过严密检视
A MYRIAD OF BYTES, NODES, AND CACHES SCRUTINIZED.
但在历经92,643个纳米级数据碎片之后
BUT FINALLY, 92,643 NANOSCOPIC DATA BITS LATER,
我们的父亲即将重归完整
OUR FATHER IS ABOUT TO BE WHOLE AGAIN.
呃 前提是这玩意儿能管用
UH, THAT'S ASSUMING THIS WORKS.
必须得成功才行
IT HAS TO WORK.
我设计的赛博机械虫传送门能将物质转化为代码
I DESIGNED THE CYBERMAT PORTAL TO CONVERT MATTER INTO CODE,
所以只要逆转默认停滞程序的正负极
SO BY REVERSING THE POLARITY OF THE DEFAULT STASIS APPLICATION,
代码就应该能重新转换回物质
CODE SHOULD BE ABLE TO BE CONVERTED BACK INTO MATTER.
听起来你已经万事俱备了 唐尼
SOUNDS LIKE YOU'VE GOT EVERYTHING COVERED, DONNIE.
是的 尤其是那些难懂的大词
YEAH. ESPECIALLY THE BIG WORDS.
好吧 我开始了
WELL, HERE GOES.
父亲 父亲 父亲
FATHER! FATHER!FATHER!
太好了 是的
ALL RIGHT! YEAH!
我们担心坏了
WE WERE SO WORRIED.
我伸了几根手指
HOW MANY FINGERS AM I HOLDING UP?
你没事吧 感觉怎么样
ARE YOU OKAY? HOW YOU FEELING?
我感觉…
I FEEL...
完整了…
WHOLE...
终于回家了…
AND HAPPY TO BE HOME...
虽然有点头晕
THOUGH A BIT LIGHT-HEADED.
物质转化过程很折磨人 父亲
THE MATTER CONVERSION PROCESS IS STRESSFUL, FATHER.
您先好好休息
LET'S GET YOU SOME REST.
瑟玲：休息
Serling: REST?
他得赶紧收拾行李
HE NEEDS TO PACK.
我们几分钟后就要出发去参加婚礼了
WE'RE SCHEDULED TO DEPART FOR THE WEDDING IN MINUTES.
哦 欢迎回来 先生
OH. AND WELCOME BACK, SIR.
呃 婚礼
UH, WEDDING?
对 凯西和艾普莉尔的婚礼
YEAH, CASEY AND APRIL'S.
总算等到这一刻了 对吧
ABOUT TIME, RIGHT?
我的孩子们 让我们欢庆这团聚的时刻
MY SONS, LET US CELEBRATE OUR REUNION.
而我认为没有比这里更合适的庆祝场所——
AND I CAN THINK OF NO BETTER PLACE TO DO SO
那就是凯西和艾普莉的婚礼现场
THAN THE UNION OF CASEY AND APRIL.
父亲 若您有此意 我亦欣然相从
FATHER, IF YOU'RE UP FOR IT, SO AM I.
让我们最终将网络空间的问题抛在脑后
LET'S FINALLY PUT THE PROBLEMS OF CYBERSPACE BEHIND US.
现在是忍者的时刻
IT'S NINJA TIME!
♪ 在城市中 现场 地下 或任何间隙 ♪
♪ IN THE CITY, ON THE SCENE, UNDERGROUND, OR IN BETWEEN ♪
♪ 有一支你从未见过的强大绿色英雄队伍 ♪
♪ THERE'S A MEAN, GREEN TEAM OF HEROES LIKE YOU'VE NEVER SEEN ♪
♪ 当恶棍与忍者龟交战之时 ♪
♪ AND WHEN THE VILLAINS AND TURTLES FIGHT ♪
♪ 这将是一场震撼的奇观 ♪
♪ IT'S GONNA BE ONE SHELL OF A SIGHT ♪
♪ 你知道海龟们与你 ♪
♪ YOU KNOW THE TURTLES GOT YOUR ♪
♪ 并肩 重返下水道
♪ BACK, BACK TO THE SEWER
♪ 少年变种忍者神龟
♪ TEENAGE MUTANT NINJA TURTLES
♪ 重返 重返下水道
♪ BACK, BACK TO THE SEWER
♪ 少年忍者神龟
♪ TEENAGE MUTANT NINJA TURTLES
点名开始
ROLL CALL!
♪ 列奥纳多 多纳泰罗
♪ LEONARDO, DONATELLO
♪ 拉斐尔 米开朗基罗
♪ RAFAEL, MICHELANGELO
♪ 我爱当一只乌龟
♪ I LOVE BEING A TURTLE
♪ 有一支你从未见过的强悍绿色英雄战队 ♪
♪ THERE'S A MEAN, GREEN TEAM OF HEROES LIKE YOU'VE NEVER SEEN ♪
♪ 他们正竭尽全力
♪ DOIN' EVERYTHING THEY CAN
♪ 阻止邪恶施莱德的阴谋
♪ TO STOP EVIL SHREDDER'S PLAN
♪ 哦耶 神龟们已经
♪ OH, YEAH, THE TURTLES ARE
♪ 回归 重返下水道
♪ BACK, BACK TO THE SEWER
♪ 少年忍者神龟
♪ TEENAGE MUTANT NINJA TURTLES
♪ 归来 重返下水道
♪ BACK, BACK TO THE SEWER
♪ 少年忍者神龟 ♪
♪ TEENAGE MUTANT NINJA TURTLES ♪
♪ 重返下水道
♪ BACK TO THE SEWER
拉斐尔：凯西奶奶的农舍 我们来啦
Raphael: CASEY'S GRANDMA'S FARMHOUSE, HERE WE COME!
要知道 拉夫
YOU KNOW, RAPH,
有些人去乡下是为了体验慢节奏生活
SOME PEOPLE HEAD TO THE COUNTRY FOR A SLOWER PACE OF LIFE.
抱歉兄弟 我可不是那些人
SORRY, BRO, BUT I AIN'T SOME PEOPLE.
我是伴郎
I'M THE BEST MAN.
我有职责在身 比如教凯西打领带...
I GOT DUTIES, LIKE TEACHING CASEY HOW TO TIE A TIE...
这可能得花点时间
WHICH, MAY TAKE A WHILE
毕竟打领带本就不是我擅长的忍者技能
SEEING AS HOW THAT AIN'T ONE OF MY BETTER NINJA SKILLS.
说真的 瑟林 我对此期待已久了
MAN, SERLING, I AM SO LOOKING FORWARD TO THIS.
我超爱婚礼
I LOVE WEDDINGS.
你什么时候参加过婚礼
WHEN HAVE YOU EVER BEEN TO A WEDDING?
参加过 从没有
BEEN TO? NEVER.
在电视上看过 一直看
SEEN ON TV? ALL THE TIME.
老兄 每部剧最后都会拍婚礼特辑的
EVERY SERIES EVENTUALLY DOES A WEDDING EPISODE, DUDE.
我没有侦测到
I'M NOT PICKING UP
任何虚拟波动或失真 主人
ANY VIRTUAL FLUCTUATIONS OR DISTORTIONS, MASTER.
数字到物理的转换
THE DIGITAL-TO-PHYSICAL CONVERSION
已完全成功
HAS BEEN A COMPLETE SUCCESS.
我很高兴听到这个消息 我的孩子
I AM GLAD TO HEAR IT, MY SON.
嘿 伙计们 我们到了
HEY, GUYS. WE'RE HERE.
他们来了
THEY'RE HERE!
斯普林特大师也来了
AND SO IS MASTER SPLINTER.
见到你们真是太好了
IT'S SO GOOD TO SEE YOU.
这让我们的婚礼更加特别了
THIS MAKES OUR WEDDING EVEN MORE SPECIAL.
完美 毫无破绽
PERFECT, EVEN.
师父 您看起来气色好极了
SENSEI, YOU LOOK LIKE A MILLION BUCKS.
呵 总比粉身碎骨强 对吧
HEH. BETTER THAN A MILLION PIECES, RIGHT?
大家快请进 放松休息吧
COME ON IN, EVERYONE. TAKE A LOAD OFF.
我跟你们说 鬼王根本毫无胜算
I'M TELLIN' YA, THE SHREDDER NEVER STOOD A CHANCE.
是的 我有所耳闻
YES, I HAVE HEARD.
我的儿子们让他们的父亲倍感骄傲
MY SONS HAVE MADE THEIR FATHER QUITE PROUD.
你呢 斯普林特大师
HOW ABOUT YOU, MASTER SPLINTER?
网络空间是怎样的
WHAT WAS CYBERSPACE LIKE?
那里……很奇特
IT WAS...STRANGE.
我完全没有单一的自我意识
I HAD NO SINGLE SENSE OF SELF,
而是拥有纷繁的思绪与情感
BUT, RATHER, A MULTITUDE OF THOUGHTS AND FEELINGS.
碎片：然而它们共通之处
Splinter: COMMON TO THEM ALL, HOWEVER,
是渴望回归家庭的深切愿望
WAS A LONGING TO RETURN TO MY FAMILY.
唐尼确实彻底解决了这个问题
WELL, DONNIE SURE TOOK CARE OF THAT.
是啊 他那聪明的大脑袋
YEAH, THAT BIG OLD BRAIN OF HIS
可是超负荷运转才把你安然无恙地救出来
WAS WORKING OVERTIME TO GET YOU OUT OF THERE SAFE AND SOUND.
对吧 对吧 对吧
HUH? HUH?HUH?
你们是在等人吗
ARE YOU GUYS EXPECTING SOMEONE?
不 所有客人都要等到早上才来
NO, NONE OF THE GUESTS ARE DUE TO ARRIVE UNTIL THE MORNING.
妈
MA?
凯西
CASEY!
那得假设凯西请柬上的日期没写错
THAT'S ASSUMING CASEY GOT THE DATES ON THE INVITATIONS RIGHT.
唉 那些字母和数字
WELL, UH, ALL THOSE LETTERS AND NUMBERS
用书法写出来都长得差不多
SEEM THE SAME WHEN YOU'RE WRITIN' IN CALLIGRAPHY.
嘿 表妹
HEY, CUZ.
呃
UHH!
出什么事了 艾普丽尔
WHAT'S SHAKING, APRIL?
什——呃...
WHA-- UH...
凯西的妈妈：别担心 凯西
Casey's Mom: DON'T YOU WORRY, CASEY.
我告诉过你表弟锡德
I TOLD YOUR COUSIN SID
要是他敢把你的特殊朋友说出去
IF HE TELLS A SOUL ABOUT YOUR SPECIAL FRIENDS,
我就敲碎他的膝盖骨
I'LL BUST HIS KNEECAPS.
这一路真是漫长啊
WHAT A LONG JOURNEY THIS HAS BEEN.
合：古一
Together: ANCIENT ONE?!
看来我得去拿备用毯子了
GUESS I'D BETTER GO GET THE SPARE BLANKETS.
毯子 真是难得的款待
BLANKETS? WHAT A TREAT.
教授  教授  教授
PROFESSOR?!PROFESSOR?!PROFESSOR?!
怎么了 各位 安吉尔
WHAT UP, GUYS?ANGEL?
看吧 这就是为什么我热爱婚礼
SEE? THIS IS WHY I LOVE WEDDINGS.
我听到了
I HEAR YOU.
没有什么比被亲友环绕更幸福的事了
NOTHING BEATS BEING SURROUNDED BY FRIENDS AND FAMILY.
我们已经掌握他们的位置
WE HAVE THEIR POSITION,
很快 以主人的名义
AND SOON, IN THE NAME OF THE MASTER,
我们将取他们首级
WE SHALL HAVE THEIR HEADS!
拉斐尔：我告诉你——兔子进洞、
Raphael: I'M TELLING YOU -- THE RABBIT GOES IN THE HOLE,
绕树一周 然后……
AROUND THE TREE, AND THEN...
瞧
VOILà!
呃
UH.
嗯
HUH?
呃 你确定这样对吗
UH, YOU SURE THIS IS RIGHT?
呃 各位
UH, GUYS?
典礼一小时后就要开始了
THE CEREMONY STARTS IN AN HOUR.
所以 开始紧张了吗
SO, GETTING NERVOUS YET?
我 紧张
ME? NERVOUS?
来吧
COME ON!
我曾单枪匹马对付整条街的帮派...
I'VE TAKEN ON ENTIRE STREET GANGS SINGLE-HANDEDLY...
与犯罪地下世界最凶残的恶徒
GONE MANO A MANO WITH SOME OF THE BIGGEST BADDIES
正面交锋过...
IN THE CRIMINAL UNDERWORLD...
对抗过怪物、变种人和外星人
FOUGHT MONSTERS, MUTANTS, AND ALIENS.
我是说 你觉得我会紧张
I MEAN, YOU THINK I'LL GET NERVOUS
就因为今天我就要结——
JUST 'CAUSE TODAY I'M GETTING MAR--
结——结——
MAR-- MAR--
哦
OH.
哇 当心
WHOA, THERE!
干得漂亮 伴郎
NICE GOING, BEST MAN.
嘿 庆幸没有怪物或变种人
HEY, JUST BE GLAD NONE OF THOSE MONSTERS OR MUTANTS
向你求婚过吧
EVER PROPOSED.
好的 艾普尔
OKAY, APRIL.
你的头纱已经准备好了
YOUR VEIL IS ALL READY.
我也负责制作了胸花
I ALSO PUT TOGETHER THE BOUTONNIERES
和花卉布置——
AND FLORAL ARRANGEMENTS --
每位宾客都有一份
ONE FOR EVERY GUEST.
谢谢你 麦奇
THANKS, MIKEY.
你是有史以来最棒的伴娘
YOU'RE THE BEST BRIDESMAID EVER.
伴娘
BRIDESMAID?!
对乌龟放尊重点
GIVE A TURTLE A LITTLE RESPECT.
我可是首席伴娘 呀啊——
I'M THE MAID OF HONOR. YAAAHH!
所以 我看起来怎么样
SO, HOW DO I LOOK?
啊
AHH!
太美了
BEAUTIFUL!
女士们先生们 这边请……
RIGHT THIS WAY, LADIES AND GENTLEMEN...
还有 呃 以上皆非的各位
AND, UH, NONE OF THE ABOVES.
跨次元的……
INTERDIMENSIONAL...
唉 我放弃了
OH, I GIVE UP.
多纳泰罗
DONATELLO.
很高兴见到你
GOOD TO SEE YOU.
你的礼物在哪儿 金
WHERE IS YOUR GIFT, GEN?
礼物 卯
GIFTS, USAGI?
我们该带礼物来的吗
WE WERE SUPPOSED TO BRING GIFTS?
好吧 我确定...
WELL, I'M SURE...
希奥米不会介意我分享他的
HISOMI WON'T MIND IF I SHARE HIS.
我猜 呃 你就是希奥米
I GUESS, UH, YOU'RE HISOMI.
莫图船长 我很高兴汇报
CAPTAIN MORTU, I'M PLEASED TO REPORT
接待处没有寿司吧
THAT THERE IS NO SUSHI BAR AT THE RECEPTION.
谢天谢地
THANK GOODNESS.
我们可不想重蹈上次的覆辙
WE WOULDN'T WANT A REPEAT OF WHAT HAPPENED LAST TIME.
我身上还有酱油味呢
I STILL SMELL LIKE SOY SAUCE.
你没事吧 皮面怪
YOU OKAY, LEATHERHEAD?
哦 没事 我很好 天使
OH, YES. I'M FINE, ANGEL.
我每次参加婚礼都会哭
I JUST ALWAYS CRY AT WEDDINGS.
嗯 基本上所有人都到齐了
WELL, THAT'S JUST ABOUT EVERYONE.
你们看见艾普莉了吗
YOU GUYS SEEN APRIL?
我没看见艾普莉 她不在这里
I HAVEN'T SEEN APRIL. SHE'S NOT HERE.
你觉得她是不是临时改变主意了
YOU THINK SHE'S HAVIN' SECOND THOUGHTS?
唉 我就知道会这样
AW, I KNEW THIS WOULD HAPPEN.
放松点 孩子
EASY, MY SON.
按照传统 新郎
IT IS TRADITION FOR THE GROOM
在仪式前不能见到新娘
NOT TO SEE THE BRIDE BEFORE THE CEREMONY.
她正在农舍里梳妆打扮
SHE IS PREPARING HERSELF IN THE FARMHOUSE.
我去接她
I WILL FETCH HER.
嗯
HMM.
那只脚
THE FOOT!
我得提醒其他人
I MUST WARN THE OTHERS.
哦 噢
OH! OH.
你不可警告任何人 鼠辈
YOU WILL WARN NO ONE, RODENT.
男人：我想知道怎么耽搁这么久
Man: I WONDER WHAT'S TAKING SO LONG.
艾普莉：嘘 各位
April: Psst! GUYS?
一切还好吗
EVERYTHING OKAY?
艾普莉
APRIL?
哇哦...宝贝
WHOA...BABE.
你看起来美——美——
YOU LOOK BEAU-- BEA--
美——呃
BEA-- UGH.
哇哦
WHOA!
放松点 迷人精
EASY, KILLER.
抱歉耽搁了
SORRY FOR THE DELAY.
斯普林特大师去找你们了
MASTER SPLINTER WENT TO FIND YOU.
你们没见到他吗
YOU HAVEN'T SEEN HIM?
没有
NO.
我在想他可能去了——
I WONDER WHERE HE COULD --
哇 斯普林特大师
WHOA! MASTER SPLINTER!
斯普林特大师...
MASTER SPLINTER...
他来了
HE'S HERE.
他——
HE'S --
这到底是怎么回事
WHAT THE SHELL'S GOING ON?
你期待已久的死期
YOUR LONG-AWAITED DEMISE.
多纳泰罗：施莱德
Donatello: THE SHREDDER?
进攻
ATTACK!
哈
HA!
我不记得收到过你的回函 没脑子的铁皮桶
I DON'T REMEMBER GETTING YOUR RSVP, BUCKET-FOR-BRAINS.
是啊 难道他们没把你炸得外酥里脆吗
YEAH. LIKE, DIDN'T WE FRY YOU UP EXTRA-CRISPY-STYLE?
或许只是我的躯体
MY BODY PERHAPS.
但你企图用来毁灭我的电流
BUT THE ELECTRIC CURRENT YOU SOUGHT TO DESTROY ME WITH
并未损伤我的数字核心
DID NOT DAMAGE MY DIGITAL CORE.
数字核心
DIGITAL CORE?
是的
YES.
我逃回了网络空间
I ESCAPED BACK TO CYBERSPACE
在那里我得以吸收汹涌而来的能量
WHERE I WAS ABLE TO ABSORB THE MASSIVE INFLUX OF ENERGY.
这股能量让我得以重组自身
ENERGY THAT ALLOWED ME TO RECONSTITUTE MYSELF
变得比以往更加强大
TO BECOME MORE POWERFUL THAN EVER.
确实 我差不多明白了
YEAH. I'M KIND OF GETTIN' THAT.
接下来只需将一行代码
THEN IT WAS SIMPLY A MATTER
感染到其中一个老鼠的数据位元上
OF INFECTING ONE OF THE RAT'S DATA BITS
当这行代码转化为物质后
WITH A LINE OF CODE THAT, ONCE CONVERTED INTO MATTER,
就变成了一个归航信标……
BECAME A HOMING BEACON...
这才让我一路找到了你……
WHICH LED ME RIGHT TO YOU...
以及这个天赐良机
AND THIS MOST AUSPICIOUS OCCASION.
哦
OH.
你闯错婚礼了 康
YOU CRASHED THE WRONG WEDDING, KHAN!
唐尼 我们去对付施莱德
DONNIE, WE'LL HANDLE THE SHREDDER.
快把斯普林特大师带离这里
GET MASTER SPLINTER OUT OF HERE.
你什么都掌控不了
YOU'LL HANDLE NOTHING.
你试图摧毁我的行为只会让我变得更快……
YOUR ATTEMPTS TO DESTROY ME HAVE ONLY MADE ME FASTER...
更强
STRONGER!
而现在你将为此付出一切代价
AND IT WILL NOW COST YOU EVERYTHING.
时候到了
IT IS TIME.
永别了 蝼蚁们
FAREWELL, WORMS.
哦 天哪
OH, DEAR!
不 不 不 不
NO! NO!NO!NO!
现在轮到你们灭亡了
AND NOW IT IS YOUR TURN TO PERISH.
等等 快看
WAIT. LOOK!
里面还有东西在动
SOMETHING'S STILL MOVING IN THERE.
唐尼 去检查一下
DONNIE, CHECK IT OUT.
我和麦基会支援拉夫
MIKEY AND I WILL BACK UP RAPH.
你弟弟逃跑是明智的
YOUR BROTHER IS WISE TO RUN.
尽管如此 他只是在推迟不可避免的结局
STILL, HE ONLY POSTPONES THE INEVITABLE.
我要把你们全部消灭
I WILL DESTROY YOU ALL.
所有人快出去 赶紧
EVERYONE OUT! HURRY!
快点
COME ON.
我们得把斯普林特大师送回运输车
WE'VE GOT TO GET MASTER SPLINTER BACK TO THE HAULER.
这很安全 而且可能是我们唯一的机会
IT'S SAFE, AND IT MIGHT JUST GIVE US OUR ONLY CHANCE
来击败施莱德
AT BEATING THE SHREDDER.
了结他们
FINISH THEM.
施莱德说他有一个数字核心
THE SHREDDER SAID HE HAD A DIGITAL CORE.
如果我们能获取该核心编码签名的样本
IF WE CAN GET A SAMPLING OF THAT CORE'S CODING SIGNATURE,
我们或许能利用它来对付他
WE MIGHT BE ABLE TO USE IT AGAINST HIM.
塞林：一个数字核心
Serling: A DIGITAL CORE?
但在这个世界里
BUT I THOUGHT IN THIS WORLD,
我以为 shredder 完全由物质构成
THE SHREDDER WAS MADE ENTIRELY OF MATTER.
我也是这么认为的
SO DID I.
但由于这个碎纸机是从维萝体内诞生的
BUT SINCE THIS SHREDDER WAS BORN OUT OF VIRAL'S BODY,
他必定继承了她的部分数字属性
HE MUST HAVE INHERITED SOME OF HER DIGITAL PROPERTIES.
那我们该如何取样呢 儿子
SO HOW DO WE GET THIS SAMPLING, MY SON?
用这个
WITH THIS!
碎纸机感染了你的一个数据位元
THE SHREDDER INFECTED ONE OF YOUR DATA BITS
因此 当转化为物质时 它便成为了这座信标
SO THAT, WHEN CONVERTED INTO MATTER, IT BECAME THIS BEACON.
若我们能将其重新转化为代码
IF WE COULD CONVERT IT BACK INTO CODE,
我们就能获得样本和所需的所有数据
WE'LL HAVE OUR SAMPLE AND ALL THE DATA WE NEED
以摧毁碎纸机 如同我们摧毁病毒那样……
TO DESTROY THE SHREDDER THE SAME WAY WE DESTROYED VIRAL...
用你的反编译冲击波
WITH YOUR DECOMPILING BLAST.
那么你觉得我们渡过难关的几率有多大
SO, WHAT DO YOU THINK THE ODDS ARE
从统计学的角度来看……
OF US GETTIN' THROUGH THIS?
很低
STATISTICALLY SPEAKING...
是吗 我倒觉得这几率刚刚提高了一点
BAD.
YEAH? WELL I'D SAY THEY JUST GOT A LITTLE BIT BETTER.
看
LOOK!
是正义力量来了
IT'S THE JUSTICE FORCE.
抱歉我们来晚了
SORRY WE'RE LATE.
哦 还有我们大家的祝贺
OH, AND CONGRATULATIONS FROM ALL OF US.
啊
AAH!
这就是你的结局
THIS IS YOUR END.
斯普林特：放开我的儿子们
Splinter: UNHAND MY SONS.
什么  哈
WHAT?! HA!
你又能拿我怎样
WHAT COULD YOU POSSIBLY DO TO MAKE ME?
就凭这个
THIS!
可悲
PATHETIC.
你根本无力击败我
YOU ARE POWERLESS TO DEFEAT ME.
我无法穿透那层护盾
I CAN'T GET A SHOT THROUGH THAT SHIELD.
它对反编译光束完全免疫
IT'S IMPERVIOUS TO THE DECOMPILER BEAM.
但或许它并非血肉之躯无法穿透
BUT PERHAPS IT IS NOT IMPERVIOUS TO FLESH AND BLOOD.
嗷
GRRR!
我绝不会向你屈服 鼠辈
I WILL NEVER FALL TO YOU, RAT.
我的目的并非要你臣服
IT WAS NOT MY AIM TO MAKE YOU FALL.
嗯
HUH?
不行
NO!
好球 干得漂亮 唐尼
NICE SHOT! WAY TO GO, DONNIE!
凯西：嘿 拉夫
Casey: HEY, RAPH.
我想我终于搞明白
I THINK I FINALLY FIGURED OUT
怎么系这个东西了
HOW TO TIE THIS THING.
凯西
CASEY!
好了 别让几颗老鼠屎坏了一锅粥
NOW, THEN, LET'S NOT LET A FEW BAD APPLES RUIN ALL THE FUN.
婚礼还得照常举行呢
I BELIEVE THERE'S A WEDDING TO BE HAD.
好
YES.
不过或许...该移到室外
BUT PERHAPS...OUTSIDE.
无论我参加过多少次这场婚礼
NO MATTER HOW MANY TIMES I'VE BEEN TO THIS WEDDING,
它总能让我落泪
IT ALWAYS MAKES ME CRY.
因此 凭借杜尼布星球赋予我的权力
AND SO, BY THE POWERS VESTED IN ME BY PLANET D'HOONNIB,
我非常荣幸地宣布你们 凯西·琼斯
IT GIVES ME GREAT PLEASURE TO PRONOUNCE YOU, CASEY JONES,
和你 艾普尔·奥尼尔 结为夫妻
AND YOU, APRIL O'NEIL, MAN AND WIFE.
你可以亲吻新娘了
YOU MAY KISS THE BRIDE.
耶 哈哈哈
YEAH! HA HA HA!
字幕由4KIDS PRODUCTIONS公司提供
CAPTIONS PAID FOR BY 4KIDS PRODUCTIONS, INC.